Guide to the Werner Pfeiffer Collection, 1953-2017
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- 3000 PRINTS
  - 3001: Drawings and Sketches of Prints
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—218)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (5.25 x 7) (3001—219)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 X 12.25) (3001—220)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—221)
    - Black and White Sketches, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—222)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—223)
    - Black and White Drawing, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—224)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (5 x 6.75) (3001—225)
    - Black and White Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—226)
    - Color Sketch, 1974; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—227)
    - Color Sketch, 1975; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—228)
    - Color Sketch, 1975; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—229)
    - Color Sketch, 1975; (8.75 x 12.25) (3001—230)
  - 3002: Early Prints, Experimental Prints, Woodcuts
    - 'Marseille' Lithograph, 1959; (14.5 x 19.5) (3002—001)
    - Proof pulled from 78 record, 1964; (15 x 17) (3002—002)
    - Proof pulled from 78 record, 1964; (15 x 17) (3002—003)
    - Proof pulled from 78 record, 1964; (15 x 17) (3002—004)
    - Proof pulled from 78 record, 1964; (15 x 17) (3002—005)
    - Proof pulled from 78 record, 1964; (15 x 17) (3002—006)
    - Proof pulled from 78 record, 1964; (15 x 17) (3002—007)
    - 'C' large woodcut, 1964; (22 x 26) (3002—008)
    - Stencil Proof no. 1, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—009)
    - Stencil Proof no. 2, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—010)
    - Stencil Proof no. 3, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—011)
    - Stencil Proof no. 4, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—012)
    - Stencil Proof no. 5, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—013)
    - Stencil Proof no. 6, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—014)
    - Stencil Proof no. 7, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—015)
    - Stencil Proof no. 8, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—016)
    - Stencil Proof no. 9, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—017)
    - Stencil Proof no. 10, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—018)
    - Stencil Proof no. 11, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—019)
    - Stencil Proof no. 12, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—020)
    - Stencil Proof no. 13, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—021)
    - Stencil Proof no. 14, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—022)
    - Stencil Proof no. 15, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—023)
    - Stencil Proof no. 16, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—024)
    - Stencil Proof no. 17, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—025)
    - Stencil Proof no. 18, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—026)
    - Stencil Proof no. 19, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—027)
    - Stencil Proof no. 20, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—028)
    - Stencil Proof no. 21, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—029)
    - Stencil Proof no. 22, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—030)
    - Stencil Grid, 1965; (25 x 22) (3002—031)
    - Color Etching, untitled, 1967; (25.5 x 21) (3002—032)
    - Letter Sprial V, relief print, 1968; (30 x 20) (3002—033)
    - Woodcut for calendar – Bird with Sun, 1969; (12 x 16) (3002—034)
    - Woodcut for calendar – 3 Birds Huddling, 1969; (12 x 16) (3002—035)
    - Woodcut for calendar – 2 Birds, red and black, 1969; (12 x 16) (3002—036)
    - Woodcut for calendar – Black Crow, 1969; (12 x 16) (3002—037)
    - Woodcut for calendar – Blue and Orange Birds, 1969; (12 x 16) (3002—038)
    - Woodcut for calendar – Black Bird Calling, 1969; (12 x 16) (3002—039)
    - Woodcut for calendar – Black Parrot, 1969; (12 x 16) (3002—040)
    - Woodcut for calendar – Orange Bird, sitting, 1969; (12 x 16) (3002—041)
    - Woodcut for calendar – Hawk Family, 1969; (12 x 16) (3002—042)
    - Woodcut for calendar – Blue Bird with red Eye, 1969; (12 x 16) (3002—043)
    - Woodcut for calendar – 2 Owls, 1969; (12 x 16) (3002—044)
    - Woodcut for calendar – Red Eagle, 1969; (12 x 16) (3002—045)
    - Woodcut – red Bird, 1969; (18.5 x 25) (3002—046)
    - Woodcut – 2 Black Birds, 1969; (21 x 27) (3002—047)
    - Woodcut of fish for calendar, 1971; (18 x 18) (3002—048)
    - Woodcut of fish for calendar, 1971; (18 x 18) (3002—049)
    - Woodcut of fish for calendar, 1971; (18 x 18) (3002—050)
    - Woodcut of fish for calendar, 1971; (18 x 18) (3002—051)
    - Woodcut of fish for calendar, 1971; (18 x 18) (3002—052)
    - Woodcut of fish for calendar, 1971; (18 x 18) (3002—053)
    - Zig-Zag – 3 dimensional print, 1974; (16 x 20 x 1) (3002—054)
    - Woodcut for 'The River' (book), 1995; (15.5 x 19.5) (3002—055)
    - Woodcut for 'The River', 1995; (15.5 x 19.5) (3002—056)
    - Woodcut for 'The River', 1995; (15.5 x 19.5) (3002—057)
    - Auto-Prints – 14 copies, 1997; (11 x 8.5) (3002—058)
    - Cast Paper over wooden shapes, 2006; (14 diameter) (3002—059)
    - Cast Paper, 2007; (13 x 10.5) (3002—060)
    - Cast Paper Grid with collage elements, 2007; (16 x 15) (3002—061)
    - Zipper Print no. 1, 1976; (38 x 24) (3002—062)
    - Zipper Print no. 3, 1976; (17 x 27) (3002—063)
  - 3003: Mixed Media Prints
    - Electric Flower – 25-15 self – linocut and circuit board, 1969; (20 x 30) (3003—001)
    - Juggler – 15-2 self – linocut and embossment, 1969; (20 x 30) (3003—002)
    - Short Circuit – 100-15 Barton – serigraph and circuit boards, 1970; (30 x 22) (3003—003)
    - Switchbox – 100-15 Barton – serigraph and circuit boards, 1970; (30 x 22) (3003—004)
    - Decend – 15-2 self – serigraph and embossment, 1970; (22 x 30) (3003—005)
    - Portable – 100-15 Barton – serigraph and embossment, 1970; (22 x 30) (3003—006)
    - Spiral – 30-5 self – shaped serigraph on mirror, 1970; (31 x 31) (3003—007)
    - ConEdison – 50-5 self – 9 serigraph on Milar, circuit board, 1970; (20 x 72) (3003—008)
    - Blackout – 100-10 AAA – linocut and circuit board, 1970; (20 x 30) (3003—009)
    - Sprout – 100-15 Barton – serigraph and circuit board, 1970; (20 x 30) (3003—010)
    - AC –DC – 10-2 self – serigraph, dycuts, embossment, 1971; (38 x 28) (3003—011)
    - Roundabout – 100-15 Barton – serigraph and circuitboards, 1971; (22 x 30) (3003—012)
    - Tired Rainbow – 100-15 Barton – serigraph and embossment, 1971; (30 x 22) (3003—013)
    - Screwed Up – 10-3 self – serigraph, 1972; (22 x 30) (3003—014)
    - Skymobile – 10-2 self – serigraph and cutouts, 1972; (30 x 22) (3003—015)
    - Prism – 250-15 Barton – serigraph, 1972; (22 x 22) (3003—016)
    - Whirl – 250-15 Barton – serigraph, 1972; (22 x 22) (3003—017)
    - Bubble Box – 100-15 Barton – serigraph and embossment, 1972; (22 x 30) (3003—018)
    - Convertible – 100-15 Barton – serigraph and circuit board, 1972; (22 x 30) (3003—019)
    - Roller Coaster – 100-15 Barton – serigraph and embossment, 1972; (30 x 22) (3003—020)
    - Trickle – 60-10 Art Club – serigraph, 1972; (22 x 30) (3003—021)
    - Running Along – 100-15 Barton – serigraph and embossment, 1973; (36 x 26) (3003—022)
    - Electric Banana – 100-15 Barton – serigraph and circuitboard, 1973; (30 x 22) (3003—023)
    - Electric Bowtie – 100-15 Barton – serigraph, embossment and circuit, 1973; (30 x 22) (3003—024)
    - Directional – 80-10 Nabis – serigraph and embossment, 1973; (22 x 30) (3003—025)
    - Downward – 80-10 Nabis – serigraph, 1973; (22 x 30) (3003—026)
    - Rainmaker – 80-10 Nabis – serigraph and embossment, 1973; (22 x 30) (3003—027)
    - Squeeze # 2 – 80-10 Nabis – serigraph, 1973; (22 x 30) (3003—028)
    - Underneath – 80-10 Nabis – serigraph and embossment, 1973; (22 x 30) (3003—029)
    - Split – 15-2 self – serigraph and embossment, (38 x 26) (3003—030)
    - Balance – 100-15 Barton – serigraph and embossment, 1974; (22 x 30) (3003—031)
    - Strings – 100-15 Barton – serigraph and embossment, 1974; (30 x 22) (3003—032)
    - Pull – 100-15 Barton – serigraph and embossment, 1974; (30 x 22) (3003—033)
    - Broken Line – 100-15 Barton – serigraph and embossment, 1974; (22 x 30) (3003—034)
    - Sunny Side Up – 100-15 Barton – serigraph, 1974; (22 x 30) (3003—035)
    - Frilly – 30-3 self – serigraph, 1974; (22 x 30) (3003—036)
    - Funnel – 50-10 Sporrong – serigraph, 1974; (22 x 30) (3003—037)
    - Silver Orbit – 50-10 Sporrong – serigraph, 1974; (22 x 30) (3003—038)
    - Pop-Up – 50-10 Sporrong – serigraph and embossment, 1974; (22 x 30) (3003—039)
    - Turnaround – 50-10 Sporrong – serigraph, 1974; (30 x 22) (3003—040)
    - Tied-Up – 50-10 Sporrong – serigraph, 1974; (30 x 22) (3003—041)
    - Spinning – 100-15 Barton – shaped serigraph on mirror, 1975; (22 x 22) (3003—042)
    - Lift Off – 100-15 Barton – serigraph and embossment, 1975; (22 x 30) (3003—043)
    - Aloft – 100-15 Barton – serigraph, 1975; (22 x 30) (3003—044)
    - Automatic Pickle – 100-15 Barton – serigraph, 1975; (30 x 22) (3003—045)
    - Flying Noodle – 100-15 Barton – serigraph, 1975; (30 x 22) (3003—046)
    - Underneath # 2 – 80-10 Stenersen – serigraph and embossment, 1975; (22 x 30) (3003—047)
    - Zipping Along – 80-10 Futura – serigraph and embossment, 1975; (30 x 22) (3003—048)
    - Tricycle – 80-10 Futura – serigraph and embossment, 1975; (22 x 30) (3003—049)
    - Rising Bubble – 80-10 Futura – serigraph and embossment, 1975; (22 x 30) (3003—050)
    - Hang-Up – 80-10 Futura – serigraph and embossment, 1975; (22 x 30) (3003—051)
    - Glassbox – 80-10 Futura – serigraph, 1975; (22 x 30) (3003—052)
    - Colored Balls – 80-10 Sporrong – serigraph, 1975; (30 x 22) (3003—053)
    - Loose Ends – 80-10 Sporrong – serigraph, 1975; (22 x 30) (3003—054)
    - Pinns – 80-10 Sporrong – serigraph and embossment, 1975; (22 x 30) (3003—055)
    - Two-Way-Boxes – 50-5 Saab – serigraph, 1976; (29 x 39) (3003—056)
    - Tingle-Tangle – 50-5 Saab – serigraph, 1976; (29 x 39) (3003—057)
    - Canopy – 80-10 Futura – serigraph and embossment, 1976; (22 x 30) (3003—058)
    - Colored Fence – 80-10 Futura – serigraph and embossment, 1976; (30 x 22) (3003—059)
    - Olé – 80-10 Futura – serigraph and embossment, 1976; (22 x 30) (3003—060)
    - Wiggling "U" – 55-5 self – serigraph and embossment, 1976; (22 x 30) (3003—061)
    - Lo-Li-Pop – 55-5 self – serigraph and embossment, 1976; (22 x 30) (3003—062)
    - Unwinding – 55-5 self – serigraph, 1976; (22 x 30) (3003—063)
    - Flip – 55-5 self – serigraph and embossment, 1977; (22 x 30) (3003—064)
    - Flap – 55-5 self – serigraph and embossment, 1977; (22 x 30) (3003—065)
    - Flop – 55-5 self – serigraph and embossment, 1977; (22 x 30) (3003—066)
    - Closed-In – 55-5 self – serigraph and embossment, 1977; (22 x 30) (3003—067)
    - Running Around – 55-5 self – serigraph and embossment, 1977; (22 x 30) (3003—068)
    - Breakthrough – 25 self – serigraph and embossment, 1973; (38 x 26) (3003—069)
- 4000 SCULPTURE
  - 4001: Drawings and Sketches
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-06; (8.5 x 11) (4001—001)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-06; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—002)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-06; (8.5 x 11) (4001—003)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-06; (8.5 x 11) (4001—004)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-06; (8.5 x 11) (4001—005)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-06; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—006)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-06; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—007)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-06; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—008)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-06; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—009)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-06; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—010)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-06; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—011)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-07; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—012)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-07; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—013)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-07; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—014)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-07; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—015)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-07; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—016)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-07; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—017)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-07; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—018)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-07; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—019)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-07; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—020)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-07; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—021)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-07; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—022)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-08; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—023)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-08; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—024)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-08; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—025)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-08; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—026)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-08; 10.25 x 8.5 (4001—027)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-11; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—028)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-11; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—029)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-11; (10 x 8.5) (4001—030)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-11; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—031)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-11; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—032)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-11; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—033)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-11; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—034)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-11; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—035)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-11; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—036)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1977-03-11; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—037)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-23; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—038)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-23; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—039)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-23; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—040)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-24; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—041)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-24; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—042)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-24; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—043)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-24; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—044)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-24; (8.5 x 11) (4001—045)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-24; (8.5 x 11) (4001—046)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-24; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—047)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-24; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—048)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-24; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—049)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-25; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—050)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-25; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—051)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-25; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—052)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-25; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—053)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-25; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—054)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-25; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—055)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-25; (9.5 x 8.5) (4001—056)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-25; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—057)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-25; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—058)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-25; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—059)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-25; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—060)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-25; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—061)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-26; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—062)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-26; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—063)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-26; (10 x 8.5) (4001—064)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-26; (10 x 8.5) (4001—065)
    - Ballpoint Pen Drawing, 1978-01-26; (8.5 x 8.5) (4001—066)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-26; (9.5 x 8.5) (4001—067)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-26; (9.5 x 8.5) (4001—068)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-26; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—069)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-01-26; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—070)
    - Ballpoint Pen Drawing, 1978-01-28; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—071)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-02-14; (9.5 x 8.5) (4001—072)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-02-14; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—073)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978-02-14; (8.5 x 11.5) (4001—074)
    - Color Pencil Drawing, 1978; (8 x 10) (4001—075)
    - Sketch Sculpture Project, 1977-09-09; (10.75 x 13.75) (4001—076)
    - Sketch Sculpture Project, 1977-09-09; (10.75 x 13.75) (4001—077)
    - Sketch Sculpture Project, 1977-09-09; (10.75 x 13.75) (4001—078)
    - Sketch Sculpture Project, 1977-09-09; (10.75 x 13.75) (4001—079)
    - Sketch Sculpture Project, 1977-09-09; (10.75 x 13.75) (4001—080)
    - Sketch Sculpture Project, 1977-09-09; (10.75 x 13.75) (4001—081)
    - Sketch Sculpture Project, 1977-09-09; (10.75 x 13.75) (4001—082)
    - Sketch Sculpture Project, 1977-09-09; (10.75 x 13.75) (4001—083)
    - Sketch Sculpture Group, 1981; (11 x 8.5) (4001—084)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-05; (8.5 x 11) (4001—085)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-06; (8.5 x 11) (4001—086)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-06; (8.5 x 11) (4001—087)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-07; (8.5 x 11) (4001—088)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-07; (8.5 x 11) (4001—089)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-09; (8.5 x 11) (4001—090)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-11; (8.5 x 11) (4001—091)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-12; (8.5 x 11) (4001—092)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-13; (8.5 x 11) (4001—093)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-13; (8.5 x 11) (4001—094)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-14; (8.5 x 11) (4001—095)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-16; (8.5 x 11) (4001—096)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-16; (8.5 x 11) (4001—097)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-17; (8.5 x 11) (4001—098)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-17; (8.5 x 11) (4001—099)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-18; (8.5 x 11) (4001—100)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-19; (8.5 x 11) (4001—101)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-21; (8.5 x 11) (4001—102)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-21; (8.5 x 11) (4001—103)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-23; (8.5 x 11) (4001—104)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-23; (8.5 x 11) (4001—105)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-24; (8.5 x 11) (4001—106)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-24; (8.5 x 11) (4001—107)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-24; (8.5 x 11) (4001—108)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-26; (8.5 x 11) (4001—109)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-26; (8.5 x 11) (4001—110)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-26; (8.5 x 11) (4001—111)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-27; (8.5 x 11) (4001—112)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-27; (8.5 x 11) (4001—113)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-28; (8.5 x 11) (4001—114)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-28; (8.5 x 11) (4001—115)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-29; (8.5 x 11) (4001—116)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-30; (8.5 x 11) (4001—117)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-30; (8.5 x 11) (4001—118)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-08-31; (8.5 x 11) (4001—119)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-01; (8.5 x 11) (4001—120)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-02; (8.5 x 11) (4001—121)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-03; (8.5 x 11) (4001—122)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-03; (8.5 x 11) (4001—123)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-04; (8.5 x 11) (4001—124)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-04; (8.5 x 11) (4001—125)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-05; (8.5 x 11) (4001—126)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-05; (8.5 x 11) (4001—127)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-06; (8.5 x 11) (4001—128)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-06; (8.5 x 11) (4001—129)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-06; (8.5 x 11) (4001—130)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-07; (8.5 x 11) (4001—131)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-08; (8.5 x 11) (4001—132)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-08; (8.5 x 11) (4001—133)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-09; (8.5 x 11) (4001—134)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-09; (8.5 x 11) (4001—135)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-11; (8.5 x 11) (4001—136)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-11; (8.5 x 11) (4001—137)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-12; (8.5 x 11) (4001—138)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-13; (8.5 x 11) (4001—139)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-13; (8.5 x 11) (4001—140)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-23; (8.5 x 11) (4001—141)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-23; (8.5 x 11) (4001—142)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-23; (8.5 x 11) (4001—143)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-24; (8.5 x 11) (4001—144)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-24; (8.5 x 11) (4001—145)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-24; (8.5 x 11) (4001—146)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-26; (8.5 x 11) (4001—147)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-27; (8.5 x 11) (4001—148)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-27; (8.5 x 11) (4001—149)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-28; (8.5 x 11) (4001—150)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-28; (8.5 x 11) (4001—151)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-29; (8.5 x 11) (4001—152)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-29; (8.5 x 11) (4001—153)
    - Black and white sketches, marker pen, 2005-09-29; (8.5 x 11) (4001—154)
- 5000 PAINTINGS
  - 5001: Painting Studies and Sketches
    - Study on Canvas, 1980; (11 x 6.75) (5001—001)
    - Study on Paper, 1980; (11 x 8.5) (5001—002)
    - Study on Board, 1983; (12.5 x 10.75) (5001—003)
    - Study on Paper, 1983; (11 x 8.5) (5001—004)
    - Study on Board, 1983; (10 x 10.5) (5001—005)
    - Study on Paper, 1983; (11 x 7.25) (5001—006)
    - Study on Board, 1983; (7.5 x 10.25) (5001—007)
    - Study on Paper, 1983; (7 x 11) (5001—008)
    - Study on Board, 1984; (5.25 x 6.5) (5001—009)
    - Study on Board, 1984; (5.5 x 7) (5001—010)
    - Study on Board, 1988; (8 x 10) (5001—011)
    - Study on Paper, 1989; (11 x 5.5) (5001—012)
    - Study on Paper, 1989; (11 x 5.5) (5001—013)
    - Study on Paper, 1989; (11 x 5.5) (5001—014)
    - Study on Paper, 1989; (8 x 4.75) (5001—015)
    - Study on Paper, 1989; (11 x 5.5) (5001—016)
    - Study on Paper, 1989; (6.5 x 9.5) (5001—017)
    - Study on Paper, 1989; (6.5 x 9.5) (5001—018)
    - Study on Paper, 1989; (8.5 x 11) (5001—019)
    - Study on Paper, 1989; (6.25 x 9) (5001—020)
    - Study on Paper, 1989; (13.25 x 7.5) (5001—021)
    - Study on Canvas, 1991; (9.75 x 8.5) (5001—022)
    - Study on Canvas, 1991; (6 x 7) (5001—023)
    - Study on Canvas, 1991; (8.25 x 10) (5001—024)
    - Study on Canvas, 1991; (8 x 10) (5001—025)
    - Study on Canvas, 1991; (7.75 x 8.5) (5001—026)
    - Study on Canvas, 1991; (17.5 x 7) (5001—027)
    - Study on Paper, 1991; (5.5 x 6.5) (5001—028)
    - Study on Paper, 1992; (7.5 x 8.75) (5001—029)
    - Study on Canvas, 1993; (5.5 x 5.5) (5001—030)
  - 5002: Shaped, Dimensional and Rotating Paintings – Drawings and Sketches
    - Collage Drawing, 1976-02-10; (10 x 6.5) (5002—001)
    - Collage Drawing, 1976-02-13; (10 x 6.5) (5002—002)
    - Collage Drawing, 1976-02-15; (10 x 6.5) (5002—003)
    - Collage, 1976-02-15; (6.5 x 10) (5002—004)
    - Collage Drawing, 1976-02-15; (10 x 6.5) (5002—005)
    - Collage Drawing, 1976-02-21; (10 x 6.5) (5002—006)
    - Collage Drawing, 1976-02-22; (10 x 6.5) (5002—007)
    - Collage Drawing, 1976-02-23; (10 x 6.5) (5002—008)
    - Collage Drawing, 1976-02-23; (10 x 6.5) (5002—009)
    - Collage Drawing, 1976-02-23; (10 x 6.5) (5002—010)
    - Collage Drawing, 1976-02-23; (10 x 6.5) (5002—011)
    - Collage Drawing, 1976-02-23; (10 x 6.5) (5002—012)
    - Collage, 1976-02-23; (10 x 6.5) (5002—013)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-11; (8.5 x 11) (5002—014)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-11; (8.5 x 11) (5002—015)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-11; (8.5 x 11) (5002—016)
    - Color Pencil Sketch, 1977-03-12; (8.5 x 11) (5002—017)